Alexander, Gabriel Additional Arbitration Files 5678
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-6, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  Recognition: Work Assignments; Handing Signs, Carpenters/Plant Guards. Closed July 7, 1976.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-7, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  Discipline: Threatening a Foreman. Closed July 7, 1976.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-8, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed August 20, 1976
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-9, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-10, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-11, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Case N-12, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-13, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  Discipline: Possession of Intoxicating Liquor. Closed August 23, 1976
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-14, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  Discipline: Abusive Language. Closed August 23, 1976.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-15, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  Discipline: Theft or Misappropriation. Closed May 2, 1977
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-16, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  Discipline: Assaulting a Supervisor, Mental Illness. Closed May 2, 1977
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-17, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  Discipline: Wasting Time. Closed May 4, 1977.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-18, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  Discipline: Threatening a Supervisor. Closed May 4, 1977.
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-19, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed June 28, 1977
- General Motors Corporation (Inland Division) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers Local 87 Case N-20, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  Discipline: Insubordination. Closed June 28, 1977.
- IUSSE Local 2000, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, Case Number 51-39-0578-77, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Closed June 23, 1978.
- Acrylic Optics Corporation and United Optical Workers Union, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Discipline: Propriety of Penalty Assessed. Closed August 26, 1977
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries and United Steelworkers of America Local 2242, Grievance 75-35, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Contracting Out: Waste Treatment Plan. Closed May 16, 1977
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries and United Steelworkers of America Local 2242, Grievance 76-1, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Working Hours; Guaranteed 40; Work contracted Out. Closed May 16, 1977
- Allegheny Ludlum Industries and United Steelworkers of America Local 2242, Grievance Number 75-40, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Safety and Health. Closed May 16, 1977.
- C and P Telephone company and Communication Workers of America (American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organizations District 2), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Discharge: False Time Report. Closed August 2, 1978.
- Cleveland Electric Illuminating Company and Utility Workers Union of America Local 270, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Discipline: Leaving Work Without Permission. Closed December 20, 1978.
- Curative Workshop and Milwaukee District Council 48, American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  Fringe Benefits, Pyramiding Vacation and Notice of Termination. Closed July 26, 1978.
- Cleveland Cliffs Iron Company and United Steelworkers of America Local 4950, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  Discipline: Severity of Penalty. Closed March 21, 1977.
- City of Detroit Police Department and Detroit Police Officers Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  Dismissal of Raymond Peterson. Closed July 26, 1976
- The Detroit Edison Company and Utility Workers Union of America, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  Discipline: Fighting. Closed August 25, 1977.
- General Motors Corporation and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 4, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  Procedure: Time Limits for Filing Grievances - Discipline Falsification of Reports. Closed April 10, 1975.
- General Motors Corporation - Pattern Makers League of North America, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  Wages: Working Hours; Shift starting and ending times. Closed June 19, 1973.
- General Motors Corporation (Detroit Diesel Allison Division) and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 4, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  Discipline: Falsification of Reports. Procedure: Time Limits for filing reports. Closed April 10, 1975.
- General Motors Technical Center and Local 1064 - United Catering, Bar, and Hotel Workers, Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union, AFL-CIO, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  Seniority: Loss of; Quit, Constructive Discharge. Theft. Closed August 1, 1975
- General Motors Corporation Fisher Body Division and the Pattern Makers League of North America, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  Recognition: Included Work: "Plastics" on Checking and Welding Fixtures. Closed June 9, 1967.
- General Motors Corporation Chevrolet Gear and Axle and United Plant Guard Workers of America Local 114, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  Discipline: Discharge for Drinking during Working Hours. Closed July 22, 1965.
- General Motors Corporation Fisher Body Division and Pattern Makers League of North America, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  Recognition: Included Work; Plastics on Checking Fixtures. Closed January 19, 1970.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  Cases H-1 through H-5: Closed November 9, 1956.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  Cases H-19 through H-22: Closed October 1, 1957
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  Cases H-8, H-23, H-24: Closed October 16, 1957.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  Case J-1: Closed April 1, 1963.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division) (Box 18, Folder 23)
  Case J-8: No date.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  Case J-0: Closed June 26, 1963
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  Case J-10: Closed April 26, 1963.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  Case J-13: Closed April 26, 1963
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  Cases J-12: Closed April 26, 1963.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Case J-14: No date.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Case J-15: Closed September 4, 1963.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Case J-16: Closed August 15, 1963.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Cases J-17 through J-20: No date.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Cases J-21 through J-25: Closed May 7, 1964.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1964 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Cases J-26, J-27: Closed August 18, 1964.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Case J-28: Closed February 11, 1965.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Case J-29: Closed January 21, 1965.
- General Motors Corporation and United Rubber Workers, Local 87 (Inland Manufacturing Division), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  Cases J-30, J-31: Closed February 17, 1965.